<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on naimcinar</title>
    <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on naimcinar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:52:26 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.naimcinar.com/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Future Lions 2024 - Submissions from the classroom</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/future-lions-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:52:26 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/future-lions-2024/</guid>
      <description> Future Lions 2024 - Submissions from the classroom This year&amp;rsquo;s Future Lions competition brief was brought by Spotify. The brief was as follows:
How can Spotify spread positivity by using technology to bring listener closer to the creators and communities they love?
Here are the submissions from my classroom:
Spotify Voice | 2024
Spotify Museum | 2024
Spotify Spotifind | 2024
Spotify Spoke AI | 2024 Spotify Spoof AI | 2024 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[TR] Sosyal Ağ Analizi ile Kadın Cinayetlerindeki Politik Kutuplaşmayı Keşfetmek - CIDA 2022 Sunum</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/cida-2022-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:33:22 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/cida-2022-presentation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Lions 2023 competition: Submissions from my classroom</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/future-lions-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:04:15 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/future-lions-2023/</guid>
      <description>Future Lions 2023: Volvo &amp;ldquo;For all life&amp;rdquo; In association with the Cannes Lions International Festival of Creativity, Future Lions is the annual global competition that challenges students to create the future. The 2023 brief comes from Volvo.
In 2023, we are asking young people to protect what is most important about our home planet – life itself. How can we pioneer the use of technology to protect people and make them feel safe?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[TR] R ile Twitter Verisi Analizi: Veri Toplama, Sosyal Ağ Analizi ve Metin Analizi Aşamaları</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/r-ile-twitter-verisi-analizi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:49:10 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/r-ile-twitter-verisi-analizi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New book chapter: Data privacy in digital advertising</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/privacy-in-digital-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 11:15:09 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/privacy-in-digital-advertising/</guid>
      <description>Our new book chapter with Sezgin Ateş &amp;ldquo;Data Privacy in Digital Advertising: Towards a Post Third-Party Cookie Era&amp;rdquo; is published as a part of the new book series from Routledge: &amp;ldquo;Algorithms and Society&amp;rdquo;. The chapter analyzes the methods by which user behaviors are tracked online for the delivery of personalized advertising and have their personal data commodified in the marketplace. The technologies employed inevitably lead to privacy violations and regulations often do not keep up with the fast pace of these technical developments which allow for ever more effective web tracking and surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Netlify CMS to an existing Hugo site</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/adding-netlify-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 22:05:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/adding-netlify-cms/</guid>
      <description>I built this web site with Hugo and host it on Netlify. I use Visual Studio Code to make all the editing on my local repository and to push to/pull from my remote repository on GitHub. I&amp;rsquo;m a beginner so this process helped me alot to learn the basic of Markdown and Git. It&amp;rsquo;s fun to update the website content following these steps but sometimes it can be frustrating. At those times, I really miss the user interface of content management systems such as Wordpress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting YouTube data with R using Tuber: Download YouTube comments</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/download-youtube-data-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:06:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/download-youtube-data-in-r/</guid>
      <description>Enable APIs The first step is to enable APIs on Google API Console. You need a Google account to do this.
Click on +ENABLE APIS AND SERVICES Type &amp;lsquo;Youtube&amp;rsquo; on the search bar. You will see four options (Youtube Data API v3, Youtube Analytics API, Youtube Ads Reach API and Youtube Reporting API). Enable all of them. Type &amp;lsquo;Freebase API&amp;rsquo; on the search bar and enable it, too. Now all the APIs are enabled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Datacamp for the classroom</title>
      <link>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/datacamp-in-the-classroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:00:10 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.naimcinar.com/posts/datacamp-in-the-classroom/</guid>
      <description>I give theoretical and prectical lessons on advertising which is in a constant state of flux. Therefore, I always try to update the content of my courses to stay relevant. Emerging technologies, current consumer trends, transformations in the media landscape, are always at the core of my lectures. Our students need to master new skills to guarantee a successful career in the media and data science is definetly one of those skılls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
